Menu

Menu

Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Policy for the website
------------------------------

This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in **mcjoe21.com**. This policy is not applicable to any information collected from outside this website unless specified.

If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to [contact us.](https://mcjoe21.com/contact)

Consent
-------

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.

Information we collect
----------------------

The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.

If you contact us directly (e.g. our contact form), we may receive information about you such as your name, email address, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide to us.

How we use your information
---------------------------

For a better experience while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your name and email address. The information that we collect will be used to contact or identify you.

We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:

* Provide, operate, and maintain our website
* Improve and expand our website with new and better content
* Understand and analyze how you use our website including what pages you visit
* Communicate with you, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other support relating to the website or support tickets
* Send you emails with the email address that you give us of first contact (deleted after a 14 days of silence)

Contact Forms
-------------

By submitting your data (including and email) via our contact form you agree to it being stored for the purpose of contacting you back on the email that you give us on first contact and will be deleted after 14 days of no activity on the ticket alone with your data given to us

Games
-----

We use the information we collect in our games (all data is anonymous), including to:

* Record game sessions including level selection data
* Improve and fix any issues in the game before major crashes
* Understand and analyze how you play our games

Childrens Privacy
-----------------

Our Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.

Log Files
---------

We want to inform you that whenever you visit our Service, we collect information that your browser sends to us that is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser version, pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.

**This document was last updated on Nov 28, 2023**

Visits: 0

© 2024 McJoe21 Dev

© 2024 McJoe21 Dev • Built with [GeneratePress](https://generatepress.com/)

Search for:
